STEPHANUS YOGI

stephanusyogi12@gmail.com || +62895604178964 || https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephanus-yogi

OBJECTIVE

My name is Stephanus Yogi. I am twenty-three years old. I have good motivation for growing, eager to learn, and can work in a team and individually. With my educational background and experiences, I am confident that my qualification and skills could make significant contributions to the program.

BIODATA

Full Name : Stephanus Pradipta Yogi Setiawan Address : Villa Bukit Tidar A2/76, Malang 65144

Place & Date of Birth: Sragen, 02 Juni 2000

Religion : Catholic

EDUCATION

| Associate Degree | Brawijaya University, | (August 2018 - July |
|------------------|--|---------------------|
| | Information of Technology | 2021) |
| | Final Project: | GPA 3.78 |
| | Design and Build a Website-Based Building Loan Information System at WidyaBhakti Malang | |
| Bachelor Degree | Brawijaya University, | (July 2021 - Now) |
| | Technical Information | |
| | Final Project: | |
| | Design and Build a Website-Based Inpatient | |
| | Medical Record Information System (Case Study: | |
| | RSI Aisyah Malang) | |

ORGANIZATION & VOLUNTARY PARTISIPATION

| Dirjen Internal Kementrian PSDM Badan | (2019 - 2020) |
|--|---------------|
| 5 | (2019 - 2020) |
| Eksekutif Mahasiswa Vocational Brawijaya | |
| University | |
| IT Support Badan Pemenangan Pemilu | (2020) |
| Kabupaten Malang | |
| Presiden Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa | (2020 - 2021) |
| Fakultas Vokasi Universitas Brawijaya | |

EXPERIENCES

Central Bank of Indonesia

Web Developer

(October 2022 - April 2023) Internship

- Create a database design and business flowcharts for the PPIP-TRACKER (Program Pensiun Iuran Pasti) website.
- Create a PPIP-TRACKER Backend API Endpoint using the PHP Laravel framework.
- Create a Pension Fund Tracker website based on the PPIP-TRACKER concept using the PHP CodeIgniter framework.

DITRESNARKOBA POLDA JATIM

(August 2022 - December 2022)

Front End Developer

Internship

- Design a list of requirements, business flowcharts, database diagrams for a case-disclosure reporting application system.
- Create a case-disclosure reporting application system using the website-based PHP CodeIgniter framework.

CWB IT DEVELOPMENT

(December 2020 - December 2022)

Front End Developer

Contract

- Slicing the Cosmetic ECommerce website design to HTML, CSS, Javascript using the PHP CodeIgniter framework.
- Consuming data from the EndPoint API that has been provided to carry out the required functions of the Cosmetics ECommerce website.

Milenial Utas (October 2020 - Now)

Front End Developer

Part-Time

• Design and build a UMKM website using wordpress with the divi builder.

Gumcode Indonesia

(March 2021 - June 2021)

Front End Developer

Contract

 Produced Interface Website Property & the CMS based on CodeIgniter and Google Maps API

Inagata Technosmith

(July 2020 - Novmber 2020)

Front End Developer

Internship

- Resolved and fixed the payment feature selection bug on property websites with React JS architecture.
- Create a Front End from the Inagata Catalog product for the portfolio for each Inagata Tech intern using the React JS architecture.

CERTIFICATES

| Junior Web Developer Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP) | (March 2022 - Lifetime) |
|---|-----------------------------|
| HackerRank Problem Solving Basic HackerRank | (August 2021 - August 2021) |
| PCAP: Programming Essentials in Pyhton | (July 2021 - July 2021) |
| Cisco Networking Academy | |

SKILLS

Programming Skills: CSS (Proficient), PHP (Proficient), React JS (Novice), Vue JS (Novice), Svelte (Novice), Laravel (Proficient).

Soft Skills: Critical thingking, Able to adapt in circumstances, Public speaking, Persistent to goals.